needmorehits.com 2017-11-16

# Privacy Policy - NeedMoreHits.com

NeedMoreHits.com understands the importance of your privacy on and off the Internet. In every action we take, NeedMoreHits.com lives up to our strict privacy statement. Whenever NeedMoreHits.com handles personal information, regardless of where this occurs, we take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy.

Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the many offerings on our website.

NeedMoreHits.com collects and retains all personal information about you that is in relation to your use of this service. This includes but not limited to your: Name, Contact Details and Billing Details. You authorize us to use this data for marketing purposes for any other NeedMoreHits.com or associated service, or associated entities.

NeedMoreHits.com may, from time to time, send you an email regarding our products or services. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information or at any point in time.

NeedMoreHits.com does not sell or provide to third parties any personal information collected as part of your use of this service, without first receiving your permission.

NeedMoreHits.com does not sell or provide to third parties any data derived from this service, aggregated or not that can be tied or linked to you personally or your account.

By accepting these terms and conditions, you agree to the use of your personal information as outlined above.

This policy may change from time to time, so please check back frequently.

| 

Login with your Trellian account   
  
---|---
